sleep and I know when I have this
feeling in the past it means I have kind
of like let go of social media
completely for a week or two and then
the next epiphany comes the next leap
comes and then I come back on and not
only is that horrible for the algorithms
of helping us get anywhere but it's not
conducive with my new mandate of sharing
the journey and sharing a little bit and
so although I'm no longer doing daily
videos on YouTube I wanted to come on
and share this piece of it this piece of
like not feeling like I'm enough to do
what I am here to do and what I am here
to do is give the piece of my journey
that helps people get through this
I now know this feeling well enough to
know that the good things come in in a
day sometimes it takes hours and it's
still hard because if you don't have the
Epiphany until you have the Epiphany and
so I'm okay with being in this space of
like feeling like crap about myself and
it don't I can't even say I feel like
crap about myself because I also I see
both sides I see like right you are who
you're supposed to be to be this thing
and also like I really wished the last
two years up and doing it I could just
write key thing down or do a succinct
edited videos that would like explain
what it is that I am trying to do in
this world as it's constantly changing
and I'm constantly changing and I also
know that if I want to get out of this
funk like if I actually want to just be
in a better mood one turn on music and
and dancing but that would not be
appropriate to do at 10:00 at night bro
and you only got to sleep tonight a huge
piece of why I'm feeling this way is
it's day one with no pot I know this is
how day when he goes and it's it's just
a constant I only didn't it for like
three days in a row it's not like I was
and then not for three days then
for three days before that so I canna
recognize the addiction cycle much
earlier now and it's I need to not think
I need to honor my addiction and be
present in it but also I'm here to serve
a higher purpose and that is a big piece
of probably why I'm feeling like
today isn't just the chemical reaction
that goes through your body when you go
off of a drug that your body likes being
on but also like literally all I have to
do to save the entire world is
meditate and stop smoking pot and even
that seems to be beyond my capability
most times and yet it is where it is
like it's it's feeling bad about that
doesn't make me smoke pot less in fact
of anything amazing wanna go smoke it
more it doesn't make me want to sit with
that emotion and I actually did meditate
today and that's the piece of I don't
know if I wanted to feel good I could
sit here and go through everything that
I have done today like today was the
federal election and I went and voted
and I listened to my heart when I voted
which didn't give me the answer I
thought it would but it did and I voted
I attended the watch party with future
thinkers and participated in that and
that was amazing this morning I enjoyed
doing that I think my teen up from
school and then it was not a president
parent I was basically just on watching
videos zoning out because that's the
space my brain was in at that point I'm
feeling like crap about that that I'm
not necessarily the best parent in the
evening that's not the point brain what
you did well I ran my kid a bath she
made her two different all a dinner and
then a secondary dinner as kids well you
didn't ask me ask you out of has to have
passed it no you asked if I wanted pesto
that pasta what you're just gonna eat it
with
spoon what's that what was gonna happen
oh but I know now having been through
this process so many times that there is
something coming on the other end and
now that I know I'm supposed to showcase
the journey anyway that is what I'm here
to do I could be more transparent I can
do it all besides also the outline
dating the online dating piece which I
guess is the problem when I have so many
social media accounts going yesterday it
became very clear yesterday was Sunday
that what I was supposed to be doing the
next step
personally which is always
interconnected with my project is to
date I knew it was coming
I knew it was gonna come eventually that
that would be the thing I'm not ready
for it in any way shape or form like no
this is gonna be me dragging my heels
and a couple people wrote to me I don't
K cubed I'm like I can't even write the
back like I just hate on my native and I
don't know how to do it in the real
world and I just people like give me a
person to actually talk to I can connect
with them maybe I don't and the issue is
then I don't like any of it
just don't like it the there isn't
enough of an incentive for me to go
through the crap I need to go through in
order today it's not stress free it is
not easy and there isn't that much of a
reward like I'm not that attracted to
people I love them as human beings but
yeah to be with one or many or like if
there isn't to nothing for a war there
to go through this and so I would
love to make friends and see if that
eventually goes somewhere but as much as
people say that online it really doesn't
work online dating doesn't work to do
that feel like I'm attracted to my not
attracted to you there's people who I
know I will never be attracted to no
matter how much we hang out because it's
they don't have a look that I'm
attracted to even once I get to know
them and they would be my best friend
and I would love them but they would not
be someone that I would want to make out
with just we
because I never felt that with guys
there wasn't ever I was like if you're
decently attractive and male when I
thought I was hetero then if I want to
be friends with you of course I want to
like be with you that's the number one
factor whereas now that I've been
friends with women my whole life there's
women I'm just like no you're my like
sister slash friend like I have zero
sexual attraction to most of women in my
life but the odd one comes around where
I'm like yes and I can even in pictures
it was so much easier so I he left and
so I be right on looks for women than it
was for that and when I was like I don't
know maybe you're a nice human being
maybe now I'm like can we be friends but
I don't know whatever wanna go with you
but this I don't know if anyone's gonna
watch this and that's not even the point
the point is - come on share when I feel
like the last thing I want to do is
share it because the other piece that
I'm doing which is why I can see that
since you can actually what's the dating
piece of it is that although I have it
all worked out in my head on how we
create a and B it isn't actually a
solution unless it's in the real world
and if I can't communicate it which is
looking more and more like it's just not
the way this is gonna happen is I have
to figure out how to redo it with people
how to co-create game B together how we
come to it and so there's a kernel of it
that I need to figure out for like this
is what I want to create who wants to
come create it with me and we'll figure
out the funding and the method of the
board of directors everything together
but every time I've attempted to do that
did I get people who are like right we
have to save sebab way and I'm like no
that's not actually what we're doing
right now like I'm not communicating it
well it's the issue like I'm like just I
just need people to talk to we can save
the world and everyone of course has a
very particular idea what that means
there's nothing wrong when he saves it
that way but that's not game B that's
not the step back and redoing something
completely new that solves it all the
issue is people want to save Zimbabwe
they don't
I created a cooperative wait but the
tech water table sidestep ah boy got it
and then I let it all like it's my fault
it's my fault that you communicate it
well and it's with not wanting to
showcase that because of shame and
because of that and I know that
like what I'm looking for is people who
want to go through this process not this
exact video because who wants that oh
come on we're about to go to sleep and
spew your vulnerability love everyone it
did I wouldn't be doing it what feels
vulnerable is actually being in that
emotion which is what being with someone
else does like it's not just the logical
part of the emotion there's so much that
is intertwined with society and culture
and like worrying about how I come off
is that it just beam and that's what I'm
here to learn all of it oh and then and
none of it I don't have to be anyone but
Who I am currently being but that's
easier said than done like this thing is
dying to get out and I don't there's
nothing I can do besides what I am doing
and yet the that it's not in the world
that I don't have the group of people to
co-create it with means that like I
haven't figured out that piece yet and I
can't even figure it out it's not a
logical thing it's an opening you Nana
unfolding and following the process till
I get there that's what I'm doing
showcase in the process it's all I can
do I think so
that was what came on today be say and
you know I feel a little more brave
since I went on public even though no
one came on I was like I'm gonna do this
in private about pretty sure it's in
public mode and
and yeah it's a public one and I was
like I don't care someone comes on the
rent to come on and if they don't they
don't and if nobody watches this good
don't watch this one it's more for me to
showcase then I can when I'm feeling
like this I don't need to pull away for
a society in fact what I need to be
doing is figuring out how to get through
this how to learn from it by just
allowing it to process hence today not
smoking pot today is huge that's huge is
I feel like crap
and it's on a crap day and I just did it
yesterday and these are the days where
it's so easy to be like one more day no
problem yet I didn't and I won't smoke
it tomorrow because tomorrow I have I
have to drive my kids somewhere in the
evening so I won't smoke it and the same
with Wednesday Thursday
they weren't Friday the day I'm allowed
to do it but I can't seem to just do it
on one day a week which means zero days
a week damn it still helping me save the
world I still have these beautiful and
that's like today I'm like right you I
feel euphoric and happy when I smoke it
especially when I haven't for a while
like myself - right now I would I'd feel
good I wouldn't feel like crap
but then tomorrow I wouldn't feel like
crap just putting it off to the world
and so I'm not and I did take melatonin
and you know what like although did you
may or not think that this is a coherent
video for 10 o'clock at night I'm
actually 10:30 at night my brain is
actually working you brain I also talked
to the first make about website today
Tommy you don't have a good memory you
forget I'm like right you voted that's
pretty big if that's all I did today I
went and voted took part of my democracy
all right hi I'm going to go sit with my
thoughts until I fall asleep but I
wanted to share whatever I just shared
with you this last 30 minutes
[Music]
yep we are gonna save the world there is
a better world on its way it's sadly
reliant on me that's not really true
there's tons of people doing amazing
work and hopefully there's someone else
out there doing this because just like
in that that piece of it that like the
more I let go that it's not me
the more it's me more I'm like because
it's not an ego thing like it's not like
I get to say it's I wish it was I can
wish who I was that personality cuz that
personality you can put this in the
world it's a like this thing inside of
me is so a solution I've had to figure
out how to become the person to put it
in the world just a hell of a lot of
self-help that it's not what normal
people like I can't listen to Tony
Robbins that's not gonna work
it's not the thing that gets us out in
the world its own here what I can't do
and having someone else do that but I
even that piece I wish I wish I could do
like if I can someone take on this task
someone take on this task I could put
out a job description but I can't even
communicate that piece of it and so I
have to surrender that I can't be
everything you can't do it all well in
no way being able to own that and
needing to be everything for this thing
and everyone to come on board and help
me and also don't touch my baby like
there's sort of personal work and I've
done a lot of that I don't like people
touching my baby no my project baby my
actual baby don't touch her she's got
she's gonna consent though so we're good
finding what my needs are in this how I
need to work with people or just need to
work myself I've done all of the earth
like there is no more planning by myself
it's will naturally happen but like how
do I follow this process with people and
I don't know I don't know how to fall in
this process of people because when
people are introduced it hinders my
process because then all of my social
anxiety and stuff catches up which is
why the online dating thing I get it I
get it universe
like seriously I have to figure out the
relationship into your connected piece
bitch it's not my strong suit has never
been my strong suit and it's because I'm
trying to tackle it in an illogical
knowledge-based way and there isn't a
Lego instruction set for dating mr.
Nowak does not exist never did I
wouldn't follow it act like this
that not happening I want to be me and
find someone else who's able to be
themselves and somehow be compatible
thought it being too much work I don't
have a lot of work to give to a
relationship we try to save the world
can't have a girlfriend as well except I
need to have a girlfriend or I need to
be in pursuit of one open to one
figuring that interconnected emotional
peace out well maybe the world in order
to be able to save the world and stop
saying it like that knowing how bad the
languages I give this thing is and also
have you know what else do I say else do
you say what any like right no I
actually do know how we can turn all of
this around easily simply everyone gets
abundance
everyone gets peace and it starts with
me and then two of us and then three of
us and eventually 10,000 and eventually
a million and seven billion and like
everyone's invited in nobody's forced
see there we go I explained it perfect
done all right I would keep it list of
how many times in a broadcast I say okay
I'm gonna go now I really am bye